A new year, a new first temple visit, with my family.
I'm supposed to meet up with Yamada to do the same thing in half an hour.
The plan is to make up some excuse, stay behind as my family leaves, and meet up with her.
It's the perfect schedule.
Oh, hey! Look, Kyo, isn't that your friend?
Hmm? That's Yamada, isn't it?
Why are you always early?
Huh? No way! Where is she? Right there!
Wow! It's her in the flesh! The real Yamada.
She's huge, huh?
She leaves that impression.
Not quite what I expected.
Quit staring at her!
You know, I forgot to ask you something very important.
Does this Yamada girl have a boyfriend?
Why do you ask?
I mean, she's all dressed up.
She keeps checking her mirror, working on her smile.
She's clearly waiting there for someone that she really likes.
Yeah, right. Whatever.
Oh, right. Silly me. My bad.
Must be imagining things. Go say hi or something.
I'll pass.
She just wants to stand by and watch me get humiliated.
Oh, man. I said I don't want to.
Come on!
Stop it! I said I don't!
Hello there, Yamada. And happy new year to you, ma'am.
Um, dear?
Oh, sorry. She's in Kyo's class.
My name is Anna Yamada.
Hi there. Don't be weird.
Mult现实的夜
花火亮
七色细色
明亮
花火焦
小细色
里头
我人的
花色
花火惠
项香
花火
バス
喜岳
美
Thank you.
もう少しで僕は僕をひとつは愛せたのに
二者様に気付けば目もわかぬまま
静かな夢の中
僕らは身も分かぬまま
Oh
Wasn't ready for that. I hope I'm not as weird as that all the time
Forget that though. This isn't exactly how I thought this would go down
You're here alone then? Yes, so I'm glad you let me join you
Way to double bug Ichikawa
Like I had a choice
Okay, we'll be waiting over here
You can't bring your hands together. It's fine. It's the thought that counts here
May all our wishes always come to be
I
What did you wish for I didn't I just wished for things to stay the same
Nothing you want to change at all
All right, then I'm headed the other way so well
Then I certainly hope that you and Kyo stay good friends this year cut it out. Sorry for intruding
Okay, just a little longer and we meet back up
Hey
Talk about super mature even a budding socialite like me could hardly keep up with her. Give me a break
Yamada did have a sort of grown-up look to her today, though
I
Am completely starving
Uh, want to drop by the udon place sure oh, I think oh sorry count us out, huh?
I
Want to make a better first impression no come on
This really the right way I think oh
Yamada
I
Want to come over to our place?
Definitely wasn't expecting this
Why did you do that? I I guess I found her charming you found her charming
Sorry to intrude like this. It's fine
I'm the one who invited you didn't expect to find you still there snacking away on everything though
Were you waiting for somebody there in particular? What oh?
Not really oh, right. Yeah, you would have to stay there if you were actually waiting for I
Bought some food I
Bought you some food to eat
You really got a chance
I
Thanks for having me my pleasure
You I told my sister I bought that Akita dog strap to match hers. What do I do?
If she sees that
I
作詞・作曲・編曲・編曲 初音ミク
編曲 初音ミク